How to make a strap that can be worn through the day
Hello everyone, this time's technique teaching class
Introduce to you how to make a strap that can be worn through the day
I believe that when you are making 3D clothing
May encounter styles that need to be added to the strap
For example, the shoulder strap of the belt skirt, the shoulder strap of the underwear, and the belt of the clothing
Take this underwear as an example
In the shoulder strap part of the underwear
Usually use a日字扣 to make a adjustment buckle
We can see that the right side of this underwear is the adjustment buckle effect that has been done
The left side is a shoulder strap effect that is sewn directly
Then how to make a real日字扣 effect on the shoulder strap on the right side?
We can use the attached model
So
There is a mutual effect between the shoulder strap and the accessory
Can make a real
The effect of the shoulder strap wearing日字扣
The current accessory model can only be used in CPU simulation
So we need to switch to CPU simulation here
Then we can take the shoulder strap on the left
Also make a wearing日字扣 effect
First, make a twist on the shoulder strap
We need to delete the sewing line between the shoulder strap
Then use the hook and loop tool
Hook the shoulder strap on the shoulder strap
At the same time, we need to adjust the fabric of this shoulder strap
And its example shoulder strap
And the conflict thickness
After adjusting the number
You can add this shoulder strap to the sewing line
Then you can choose it in the 3D window
Click the right button to add it to the inside
Switching the view can see the current version of this shoulder strap
Just add it to the inside
Open simulation
Here, in order to prevent shoulder strap
In the simulation process, there is a misalignment
You can add a row of fixed needles on one side of the board
Switch the tool to the fixed needle
Comparison
Then add a row of fixed needles to the double-sided mouse in the center of the outside of the board
Then here
Add a ring component
We can find the corresponding ring component in the close library
You can also choose the component type in Connect
Then enter the component name
Search
Here we can
Copy the existing ring component in the current project file
Then drag it into the 3D window to add it in
At this time, we can choose this component
Use the symbol in the upper right corner of the component
Arrange it near the position of the ring
Then use the positioning ball
Move component
Then come to the other side
You can see that the current board has not passed the ring
So we can use
Select the grid comparison tool
Select all the grids on the back of the small board
Then use the positioning ball
Move it forward, that is, towards the direction of the screen
Then you can look from the side
The effect of this ring is made
Due to the copy simulation, the copy is between the board
Is interactive
So it is recommended
If there is a cross between the board and the copy
You can use the selection grid tool
Select the area of the surface
Drag it out
Open the simulation
We can see
The current ring effect is also made
Next, make the twist of the shoulder strap
First, you can turn on the simulation
Put this shoulder strap board
Through the fixed needle movement
Make it close to the ring component
Then turn off the simulation
Next, make the shoulder strap twist board
First use the selection grid tool
Take the shoulder strap twist board out
Then we can give this board
Appliance shoulder strap fabric
At the same time, you can adjust its particle diameter
And its conflict thickness
Then increase the sewing line
Then add it to the inside
Then you can see that the board here has been added to the inside
Then you can use the positioning ball
Adjust the board inside
Make it pass through the circular board
Next, you can delete the fixed needle here
Here you need to pay attention
Because the shoulder strap board is flexible
So in order to make this simulation more stable
We can freeze this ring
And can be on the right side of the attribute editor
Adjust the conflict thickness of the ring
For example, change it to 0.5
This is attached
The gap between the boards
Will become smaller
Then we can turn on the simulation
At this time this board
There is also a pass with the accessory
So you can use the selection grid tool
Select the pass grid on the board
You can also make a frame selection in the 2D window
After selection, you can adjust its position in the 3D window
Then turn on the simulation
In this way, the board is flipped
The effect of the ring is also made
Because the shoulder strap should be a complete board
So you can merge them into a complete board
Here
You can delete this sewing line here
Then you can turn on the simulation
Turn off the simulation
Then we wear the日字扣
We can be in the close library
Select the attached hardware accessory
Insert this日字扣
You can also download and use the corresponding material in Connect
Next, adjust the position of this日字扣
Use the compass in the upper right corner of the positioning ball
Then come close to the keyboard
Then adjust the position of the accessory
To determine the position of the日字扣
You can display it in the clothing information
Select the display internal line
Then put the center of the日字扣
Near this internal line
Here
In order to make the accessory between the keyboard and the board
The keyframe can be smaller
You can adjust its conflict thickness
In order to control the position of the keyframe
We can also freeze this accessory
Select the right key to freeze it
Next, you can use the selection grid tool
Select this internal line
Double click to select the grid on this line
Then use the positioning ball to drag it out
In this way, we can see
The board has passed the日字扣
This part is done
Then you can turn on the simulation
Check if the board has a pass
You can see that there is a pass here
So we can select this part of the grid
Drag it out
Then we can turn on the simulation
And turn off the simulation in time
Next
We make the effect of the shoulder belt
The effect of the shoulder belt
That's the pass effect of this part
First
You can make a small part of the pass
Made
That is to say
On the left and right sides of this internal line
Increase two internal lines
Do the position of the pass board
We can select this internal line
Click the right button
The internal line diameter
On both sides of it
Add
A 5 mm internal line
This is also the width of the pass board part
Click to confirm
Then you can use the selection grid tool
Select these lines
Then click the right button
Selection as board
Then adjust the fabric of the board
And its particle diameter
Thickness conflict
Then sew this board to the inside of the shoulder belt
Then add it to the inside
Here you can find
The current board
The center has not passed through this日字扣
So we still need to do it again
Use the selection grid tool
Select the grid in the middle of the board
Then push it in
Then select the grid in the middle of the board
Make it pass through the part in the middle of the日字扣
After adjustment
We can put this board
Sewed together with one end of the shoulder belt
We can move the board to the top
Then delete its original sewing line
Because these two sewing lines
Are supporting us to make the buckle
Then we need to give the board a 10mm inner line
Convenient for us to sew
The distance is 10
Click to confirm
Then add the sewing line
And turn on the simulation
You can see
This buckle effect is also done
Then we can delete one of the sewing lines
Then make it the only complete shoulder belt
So we need to collect them together
Mesh together
If re-em sibling to see
You can see
The inner shoulder button quéht氣 м Afghanistan
Check the situation if the window is blocked.
We can use the Select Browse tool to adjust its position.
We can click on the 3D window to locate it.
Then select the blocked part.
Then adjust its position in the 3D window.
That's all.
This is the effect of passing through the sunshade.